Groucho & Cavett is a documentary film directed by Robert S. Bader.
Discover the enduring friendship between television personality Dick
Cavett and his mentor iconic comedian Groucho Marx.
Their relationship is chronicled through interviews with Cavett,
archival footage and interviews with George Burns and others.
Self, played by Dick Cavett.
Self (archive footage), played by Groucho Marx.
Self (archive footage), played by Jack Paar.
Self (archive footage), played by E.Y. Harburg.
Self (archive footage), played by Woody Allen.
Self (archive footage), played by Shelley Winters.
Richard Alva Cavett ( KAV-it; born November 19, 1936) is an American
television personality, comedian and former talk show host.
He appeared regularly on nationally broadcast television in the
United States from the 1960s through the 2000s.
In later years, Cavett has written an online column for The New York Times, promoted DVDs of his former shows as well as a book of his Times columns, and hosted replays of his TV interviews with Bette Davis, Lucille Ball, Salvador Dalí, Lee Marvin, Groucho Marx, Katharine Hepburn, Judy
Garland, Marlon Brando, Orson Welles, Woody Allen, Ingmar Bergman, Jean-Luc Godard, Robert Mitchum, John Lennon, George Harrison, Jimi Hendrix, Richard Burton, Sophia Loren, Marcello Mastroianni, Kirk Douglas, Mae West and Bobby Fischer, among others, on Turner Classic Movies.